(upbeat music)
Luke Skywalker and Han Solo
rescue the princess, destroy the Death Star,
but their story didn't end there.
(upbeat music)
(loud booming)
Now, the creators of the biggest smash hit of all time,
bring you the next episode in the "Star Wars" saga,
"The Empire Strikes Back."
(Chewy growling)
(guns firing)
(loud bomb exploding)
The continuing story of our band of heroes.
Luke Skywalker, Princess Leia,
Han Solo, C3PO,
R2D2 and Chewbacca
and introducing Lando Calrissian.
It's an epic of romance.
(upbeat music)
Of heroes and villains.
(Chewy growling)
(electronic noises)
They cross trackless voids to unknown worlds.
(upbeat music)
(loud screeching)
(loud booming)
A galactic odyssey against oppression.
(loud smashing)
(upbeat music)
A big new sprawling space adventure in the "Star Wars" saga,
"The Empire Strikes Back."
(loud explosion)
Coming to your galaxy next summer.
(Darth Vader breathing)